[
    {
        "question": "What is RealVisXL?",
        "answer": "RealVisXL is an AI model by SG_161222 that excels in generating lifelike characters, landscapes, buildings, and objects, ideal for non-commercial research."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the size of the RealVisXL model?",
        "answer": "The size of the RealVisXL model is 6.46 GB."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the creator of RealVisXL?",
        "answer": "The creator of RealVisXL is SG_161222."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of model is RealVisXL?",
        "answer": "RealVisXL is a Checkpoint type model."
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of images does RealVisXL specialize in generating?",
        "answer": "RealVisXL specializes in generating images of characters as well as realistic landscapes, buildings, and objects."
    },
    {
        "question": "How does RealVisXL compare to the SD 1.5 version?",
        "answer": "RealVisXL creates more lifelike characters compared to the SD 1.5 version, with a significant improvement in results, and it also includes the Inpainting model."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base model of RealVisXL?",
        "answer": "The base model of RealVisXL is SDXL Turbo."
    },
    {
        "question": "Is RealVisXL licensed for commercial use?",
        "answer": "No, RealVisXL is licensed under the Stability AI Non-Commercial Research Community License and is not intended for commercial use."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the dimensions of the batch size used in RealVisXL's sample images?",
        "answer": "The batch size used in RealVisXL's sample images is 896x1152."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the settings for KSampler used in the creator's sample images?",
        "answer": "The settings for KSampler used in the creator's sample images were: Steps: 8, Seed: 1383965240, Sampler: DPM++ SDE, Scheduler: Karras, CFG scale: 1, Denoising: 0.35."
    }
]